Question reality. Discover truth.
Levels is a science fiction, action, thriller film directed by Adam Stern.
After witnessing his girlfriend's murder, a man risks everything -
including reality itself - to discover the truth.
Ash, played by Cara Gee.
Joe, played by Peter Mooney.
Hunter, played by Aaron Abrams.
Oliver, played by David Hewlett.
MEL, played by Amanda Tapping.
Geddes, played by Adam Hurtig.
Levels is a 2024 Canadian science fiction action film written and directed by Adam
Stern and starring Cara Gee, Peter Mooney, Aaron Abrams and David Hewlett.
The film explores themes of artificial intelligence (a.i.), virtual
reality, computer simulation, cyberpunk, augmented reality.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.